Through
the void we glide so steady and true.
A starship of mercy with a 10,000 crew.
Lights pulsing rhythm like a heartbeats
glow.
Carrying hope when the story lines glow.
Vega still
flies
through the dark where the silent cries.
Healing hands
across the skies.
Hospital starship
never dies.
And a w spread wide through the cosmic
cold.
Saving lives where the stories unfold.
Planets whisper, they know our name.
Vega answers every time the same.
One mission, one greed to heal every
need. Vega still
flies
through the dark where the silent cries.
Healing hands
across the skies.
Hospital Starship. Faker never dies.
One mission, one creed to heal every
need.
Vega sails. Vega flies
through the dark where the silent cries.
Healing hands
across the skies.
Hospital starship faker never dies
as we sh the unknown.
Every soul matters. No one's alone.
The wormhols and walkers our banners
will soar. Bringing peace to the
farthest shore.
Galaxies turn as we chart the unknown.
Every soul matters. No one's alone.
Through wormholes and wonders, our
banners will soar. Bringing peace to the
farst shore.
Heat. Heat.